DAVID **CLARK**

11 Evan Court Fishkill NY 12524 · 303.921.9693

<u>David.clark12@gmail.com</u> | <u>https://www.linkedin.com/in/davidmclark12/</u>

Developer with more than 20 years of experience working with technology in the finance sector. Skills range the gamut from AWS and Elasticsearch to C# and Angular. Possess strong abilities in the DevOps area and proven ability to deliver on large scale projects.

EXPERIENCE

SEPT 2019 – DEC 2019

SRE, REMEDY PARTNERS

Site Reliability Engineer for Remedy Partners, a leading company in health care bundled payments. Worked with the team supporting legacy EC2 instances running mysql and Mongo DB as well as current gen systems running as micro services. Specifically, web api with kinesis streams, lambdas, Dynamo DB and Redis.

- Stood in as temporary dba.
- Wrote python scripts to automate pulling credentials from aws to reset passwords, create new users etc. for mysql and postgres.
- Automated the generation of NewRelic alerts for new lambda functions to monitor such things as IteratorAge etc.
- Daily support of cloud formation templates and using tools like cfn-nag, init etc., ensuring CIDR blocks were within compliance along with open ports etc.
- Experimental use with AWS CDK, which is still in beta, allowing for CloudFormation templating through code such as python, node, java, .net core or go.

DEC 2018 - SEPT 2019

PERSONAL SABBATICAL

Took a personal sabbatical to take care of family and travel. Returned to the job market around June or July of 2019.

NOV 2017 - DEC 2018

DEVOPS ENGINEER, MILLENNIUM MANAGEMENT

Sole DevOps support engineer for the Data Analytics group, working with them on a daily basis. Responsible for automation, support and release of the Falcon project which pushed all firm communications data to an Elasticsearch cluster stored on 40+ Amazon EC2 instances. Application is used for easy searching and flagging by compliance for potential SEC violations.

- Managed both on prem and cloud code through Git and AWS Code Commit
- Established numerous CI/CD pipelines through Jenkins that automated on prem code builds through Git which in turn uploaded to AWS S3 to trigger AWS Code Pipelines
- Created numerous bash scripts to pull monitoring data from RabbitMQ and Elasticsearch for integration into ITRS Geneos for monitoring

- Maintained Ansible scripts for AWS deployments to EC2 instances for applications like ElasticSearch, Kibana, RabbitMQ, Nginx and Datadog
- Sat with data analytics team for daily standups and weekly sit downs with the business
- Created and maintained all application documentation through Atlassian Confluence
- Responsible for multiple migrations of roughly 120 TB of data from one ElasticSearch cluster to another, typically when moving from one AWS AMI to another
- Maintenance of the Falcon application while creating various data filters through the use of Python and updates to UI through Django, Angular 5 and Sales Force Lightening Design
- Created and maintained all Tidal Enterprise Scheduler jobs for automation of daily ingestion of Bloomberg, Reuters, Pivot, ICE, Slack and Skype data
- Use of Kibana, Postman and CloudWatch coupled with custom scripts to provide insight into any issues that would impact the application

NOV 2010 - OCT 2017

DEVOPS / SOFTWARE DEVELOPER, YORK CAPITAL MANAGEMENT

Creation and support of numerous internal applications built with C#, Angular, Bootstrap, Font Awesome and SQL Server. Also responsible for support of 3rd party application such as EzCastle OMS, Geneva Fund Accounting system, MIK Datawarehouse, Electra Reconciliation and various data feeds like Bloomberg SAPI and BPIPE.

- Helped create a web version of the MIK real time PnL application that was also accessible through mobile devices
- Worked to integrate a custom restricted list application with EzCastle and Geneva
- Created a custom change management system through the use of C#, Angular, SQL Server and Nancy
- Creation of numerous web services using TopShelf e.g. automatically uploading data from a shared drive to an Azure web server or upload files to an AWS S3 bucket
- Responsible for the migration of MIK Bloomberg data integration from SAPI to BPipe
- Daily support of numerous 3rd party applications supporting middle office such as;
 - Electra Staars Trade Reconciliation
 - MIK DataWarehouse
 - Geneva Fund Accounting
 - o Tidal Enterprise Scheduler Automation of daily feeds
 - Eze Castle OMS
- Creation of daily ETL feeds for upload to various prime brokers
- Maintain build automation through the use of Team City and Octopus deploy

NOV 1997 - NOV 2010

SYSTEMS ENGINEER / PROGRAMMER ANALYST, OPPENHEIMERFUNDS

Held numerous positions over 13 years. Starting as a tape librarian in the data center moving up to computer operator, prod support specialist, sr. support specialist, associate Unix administrator, manager of third shift operations, programmer analyst and sr. programmer analyst.

- Responsible for the migration of NYC data center to Denver after 9/11
- Oversaw the move of all daily reporting to Actuate
- Led a team of 6 as 3rd shift manager of Operations
- Completely re-wrote the NY nightly batch processing through Autosys and Sybase stored procedures. Moved from consistently missing a 06:00 SLA to typically having processing done before 03:00 every morning

• Headed the upgrade of Sybase from 12.0 to 15.0

EDUCATION

AUG 2004 BS CIS, DEVRY

Degree from DeVry university with roughly 3.83 GPA.

SKILLS

- SQL, C#, TopShelf, MVC, MVVM
- HTML, JavaScript, CSS, Bootstrap, Font Awesome, Sales Force Lightening Design, NPM, Gulp, Grunt, Bower, NodeJS, Django, Angular, JSON, Nancy, Yarn, Nginx, Celery, GUnicorn, Troposphere, Docker (Self Training), Kubernetes (Self Training), Artifactory
- Bash, Python, PowerShell
- CentOS 6.x, 7.x, Windows, Windows Server
- ElasticSearch, Kibana, RabbitMQ, Ansible, Jenkins, TeamCity, Octopus, LogStash (Minimal)
- MIK, Geneva, Electra Staars, EzeCastle
- Git, TFS
- AWS, CloudWatch, CloudFormation, Dynamo DB, Mongo DB, kinesis, lambda, CodePipeline, CodeDeploy, CLI, CodeCommit, EC2, Lambda, ASG, IAM, ELB, S3, Route53, VPC, Postman
- Tidal Enterprise Scheduler, Autosys
- Jira, Confluence
- Market Data
 - o Bloomberg SAPI, BPipe
 - o Thomson Reuters
 - Factset
 - o Ice
 - Markit
 - Moody's
 - $\circ \quad MorningStar \\$